freeclassifiedssites.com 2017-11-20

# Free Classifieds Sites - Privacy Policy

FreeClassifiedsSites.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the FreeClassifiedsSites.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

What personally identifiable information is collected 

Registration is not required to post listings on FreeClassifiedsSites.com. Subsequently, the FreeClassifiedsSites.com does not collect any personally identifiable information on its users. What little information we do collect is for the purpose of ad posting is provided by you. This mainly consist of your email address for the purpose of sending user replies in response to your ad. We don't engage in any cross-marketing programs with any sites nor do we send unsolicited communications for marketing purposes.   
When posting ads at our site, the users have the option on whether or not they would like to reveal their email address. User may choose, if they prefer, to use our private email messaging system that provides user anonymity and helps reduce email harvesting and spam. 

What else you should know about your online privacy 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in ads that you post or through email \- that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.   
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining your password and personal information. Please do not post any personal information on FreeClassifiedsSites.com that you expect to keep private. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.   
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, FreeClassifiedsSites.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

Data We do collect and store 

All listings posted in FreeClassifiedsSites.com are stored in our database for 90 days, then they are automatically deleted by the system. Once they are deleted, they are off our system for good. They are not stored nor achieved other than standard backups during the same 90 day period.   
Our web logs track standard web site statistic by users such as I.P. addresses and access information. The primary goal of the web logs is in collecting web site usage statistics. This information is used solely to provide us with statistical analysis of site usage and popularity. This is standard web site data used by most site. We keep our web logs for about 30 days then delete them from our system. 

How FreeClassifiedsSites.com protects children's privacy 

FreeClassifiedsSites.com is a general audience web site. Children should always ask a parent for permission before viewing or posting any ads online. FreeClassifiedsSites.com does not collect any information from persons under the age of 13 nor does it share any user information with third parties regardless of age. If we learn that a listing has been posted by a person under the age of 13, FreeClassifiedsSites.com will remove that post. 

With whom your information may be shared 

As a general rule, FreeClassifiedsSites.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below.   
FreeClassifiedsSites.com may disclose email or I.P. information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Use of FreeClassifiedsSites.com or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the FreeClassifiedsSites.com, other users of the FreeClassifiedsSites.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
